Mohamed Ahmed Abdel Majeed

Al Madinah, Saudi Arabia

Mobil: (+966 55 678 8870)

E-mail: Mohamedabdalmajeed99@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mohamed-ahmed-abdull-majeed

OBJECTIVE

A driven and accomplished accounting professional with over 2 years of experience in diverse accounting roles, excelling in branch supervision, financial reporting, tax preparation, and reconciliations. Possesses strong analytical and problem-solving skills, demonstrated leadership capabilities, and a commitment to accuracy and efficiency. Seeking a challenging accounting manager position at Najmat Tabah Company to leverage expertise and contribute meaningfully to the company's financial success.

EDUCATION

BSC. Faculty of commerce English section, Al-Azhar University

2016-2020

Department: Accounting

Grade: Good

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth:

1/12/1997

Military service: Performed

Marital status: single

VOLUNTEER

Azhar Dream

- Delegate Accounting
- Delegate entrepreneurship

Eng break

Member Marketing

TEDx SHA

Event management

EXPERIENCE

Accountant manager at Najmat Tabah Company (10-2023-current)

- Responsibilities included:
- Supervising supermarket branches
- Supervising fabric, silver, and accessories stores
- Preparing monthly income statements and sales reports for all branches
- Filing taxes for the branches
- Making settlement entries
- Preparing trial balances
- Bank reconciliation

General Accountant at Najmat Tabah Company

(05-2023-10-2023)

- Responsibilities included:
- Registering purchase invoices
- Preparing sales reports
- Matching supplier balances
- Bank reconciliation

Accountant at esnad for trading consulting & logistics support ((05-2022)-(10-2022))

- Track customer shipments
- Prepare Initial claims
- Follow-up of customer account balances
- Statement of account
- Balance matching during the period
- Preparing the report of transactions
- Following up with all company departments and solve any issue occurred for any client
- Determine the Estimated costs for each process of clearance and arrange with the clients for payment process also handles the old required balance from the clients to the company Customs or the shipping line.
- Deal with the new company clients and set their contract terms including all process and costs
- The LAVA ERP program is used in this period

Sales at El Hamed retail market

(2018-2020)

- Buying goods from factories and wholesaler
- Carrying out the sale and collection process
- Statement of account
- Follow-up of customer account balances
- Make a periodic inventory
- Follow up supplier's payment

SKILS

Language

- **Arabic (**Mother Tongue)
- English: Good (writing, reading& listening).

Computer

- LAVA ERP: Very good
- MS office
- Word: Very goodExcel: Very good
- PowerPoint: Good

PERSONAL

- Honest
- Diligent and organized
- Ethical and loyal
- Punctual
- Flexible
- Team player
- Creative
- Technologically competent
- Problem solver